{ 
   "questions":[ 
      { 
         "question":"Which of the following is not a design pattern?",
         "level":3,
         "answers":[ 
            "Comparative",
            "Strategy",
            "Adapter",
            "State"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":0
      },
      { 
         "question":"Which is not a maintenance risk?",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "Schedule",
            "Low Quality",
            "Standardization",
            "Loss of Control"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
      { 
         "question":"Which is not a type of maintenance?",
         "level":3,
         "answers":[ 
            "Corrective",
            "commutative",
            "Adaptive",
            "Perfective"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":1
      },
      { 
         "question":"Which of the following role is not present at the scrum meeting?",
         "level":1,
         "answers":[ 
            "Product owner",
            "scrum master",
            "Customer",
            "developer"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
      { 
         "question":"Which Design Pattern allows only one appearance of each object?",
         "level":1,
         "answers":[ 
            "Factory",
            "Singleton",
            "Memento",
            "Adapter"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":1
      },
      { 
         "question":"Which stage does not exist in the life cycle of software quality assurance?",
         "level":3,
         "answers":[ 
            "Design",
            "Implementaion",
            "Marketing",
            "Support & maintenance"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
	  { 
         "question":"Which factor does not characterize the maintenance phase?",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "The longest",
            "the most expensive",
            "The cheapest",
            "Combines all the steps"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
	  { 
         "question":"Which of the following is not Types of Black Box Testing?",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "Functional Testing",
            "Non-functional testing",
            "Loop Testing",
            "Regression Testing"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
	  { 
         "question":"Which of the following is not Types of White Box Testing?",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "Regression Testing",
            "Path Testing",
            "Loop Testing",
            "Condition testing"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":0
      },
      	  { 
         "question":"Which of those is interaction diagram that detail how operations are carried out.",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "Use Case Diagram",
            "Class Diagram",
            "DFD",
            "Sequence Diagram"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":3
      },
      	  { 
         "question":"Which of the following is not part of iso9000 philosophy?",
         "level":2,
         "answers":[ 
            "Document what you do",
            "Document what you feel",
            "Record what you did",
            "Do what you document"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":1
      },
            	  { 
         "question":"What is a reason to get certificate of iso9001 to an organization?",
         "level":3,
         "answers":[ 
            "Certificate is a bussiness decision",
            "Certificate is a must for every SW company",
            "Certificate is a tool to get more resources from the government",
            "Certificate is obsolete and is not relevent for nearly 20 years"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":0
      },
            	  { 
         "question":"Which of the following is describing agile methodology?",
         "level":1,
         "answers":[ 
            "Rigid planning, slow development, delivery probably not on schedule, and slow improvement",
            "work by phases: analysis, design, code, test. when you finish a phase, move to next phase.",
            "Adaptive planning, evolutionary development, early delivery, and continual improvement",
            "take your time to make the best product for the customer"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":2
      },
              	  { 
         "question":"Which of the following is not one of norman design principles?",
         "level":1,
         "answers":[ 
            "Feedback",
            "Affordances",
            "Consistency",
            "Proximity"
         ],
         "team":"Spider",
         "correct_answer":3
      }
	  
   ]
}